--This is a Fan sub--
-Please improve this sub-
If I had known how bad things will go, i would have done everything differently.
...
No one company in one of the most wanted.
I am Benjamin this is my story
WHOAMI
Hello mouse I know and have just provided hackers-howami 110 friends of the Russian Cyber Mafia evaporator seduce talk to him
And you're ,.. WHOAMI?
There's a reason why you are here
There's a reason why to why I'm right here
also
...
all are somehow connected
it is not a fan of a beginning and an end has
it is from a network
and I in the middle
Thomas,..
I always wanted a super keeps his or super cut
I wanted to do things that no one possible
Ilbenstadt I already had a superpower us
Superhero costume you already
Every superhero have the tragic family history
Spiderman 2.
Death Metal rare, rare Superman
my father before I was born to France Akan
the only keepsake that he has Saturn Hilden has brought the friend from Russia
My mother took her own life.
best material for a heroic story
Number for taking care of me later I me they
I'm not a psychologist
a woman and a mistake I do not know about you three further connection to the FRIENDS
everything you want to know
but not every detail
Hacking is like magic
the point is to mislead others
Work it comes to others to do.
Since I was 14 I had my Thunder times in the law.
Programming class my first theme universe as infinite possibility for the first time, I feel that I feel
world zero below 1000 lira in Frick
TV already great her my first topic
Universe of infinite possibilities
for the first time, I felt good
sorry but nothing poems to be this feeling that
good food world a zero below 100 Geek
E330 and ones geek in peace does not answer to you a
Zero below 100 Geek
a Freak
but nothing is not among them
the catch basin for people who me in a different time
Word 2007 to you and so-called day
here I can be as I previously
here i can has its right and do not sleep get settled
not after
But there was.
it does not work
I had the idea of Immoscout world.
YT outside cable 1 Saar ladies and
YT outside cable 1 was not for me.
MRX
do not expect that no one knows who is what
Do not expect that no one knows who did what. famous
Do not expect that no one knows who did what.
To serve lamps light soup
To serve lamps light the.
in the state of an experiment we manipulated prescriptions
Ritalin Scott
Made to Ritalin
Alexander III revenge
rule 1:
rule 2:
erfan space and needs space to say
the fun is not only the virtual world
but the real reason I'm sitting why everything is so
happens, it is Marie
** ** slence
Berlin of them helped the hope is the rainbow over
the cascading stream of life
Examination SMS without plan or should one in Berlin. Santos
100 in the period Trailer
bird
pizza
fallen in love with me during school hours
110 years nobody remembers more on the fingers of the
last row
even today
you apologize, Natasha
the world does not need a savior, but now I can call people
it's okay,
thank you
freak
Marie has a problem and I was able to solve it, I have to tell you only the exam questions
Please texting Winfried.
marry in Rio.
bingo
Questions for the Bachelor examination 3 set on the server of the University of Zurich
18 clock access
Rain is only one nice ride system and
Brune what inside other
and some take
I was a fool
no entries no criminal record do 50 hours of community service
sebalters their life is in your hands
Social hour consisted instead Service, that I do not at
are always everything so that it can find a beat
And what are you doing now.
...
computer Crime
and you?
this and that
Bad Merzigine?
Botnet? phishing?
or you're feeling scriptkiddi
for hacking a server..
Zero Day exploit
you can not just me
...
I'm Max
Benjamin
Do you like a party?
Carpet Lidl asked whether one moment even the machine
ran together
Do you run it all behind in a country?
Yo guys this is Benjamin
to speak the complete opposite of me charismatic winner
Stefan
Benjamin
Benjamin Engel
Stefan traffic accident master hand in each program manager
can atter Paul
hardware freak Tübingen paperclip and Madame you everything
Had I your mother f *** son. I had your mother
f ***** and rich father Shoppyland boarding
So must be the first
...
Thomas works out
* Typing *
jackpot
Paul
Benjamin
-
Come on lets go..
Come
You are the pizza boy...
You know her?
-
This is a private party
then what?
I always have the other Kaltenbach
STOP
-
Your Bengamin arent you?
Benjamin Engel
--♪--
good ...
my grandmother was diagnosed four years ago with Alzheimer's
poisoned every day an invisible eraser at their contours
The tickets please.
The tickets please no advertising Kaufland.
Whats wrong?
this is our stop.
come lets go..
Come
what is between us and Spa
Universe had come to send
be classified no idea what's going on
security prison outside I roll up no idea what's going on
yes there is it
MRX
Exactly
distally trouble with honey crust concentric social engineering
with social engineering you can do what you know what water
without access
to
here take this
Watch and learn
===
Where are we going?
♪
come
what are you looking at..
lets go
What is happening
This is not a game my boy
no
this was our first joint action lesson of something big
Do I need to know if what you tell me and I a part of
I know if what you're telling me determined.
please
max has an idea
and
if Max had 1 ID then be unstoppable anchor
bingo
how about clay and clowns laughing at you Miley Cyrus and Liam Hemsworth
CLAY
Our next destination was a big company
who is behind this is it is a criminal organization or simply a group of Teenagers
AI.. Marri
Benjamin
Hello
you called me?
not me
you?
not that i can remember
single tragedy
you feel sorry for you that you are
you are cool
night is still young
MRX is not interested in a damn for us because out there were other big players
I look forward to the cooperation
good
max was right I had something up right changes
so how did you got this?
Employee of the Month
Stay away from her
I ask myself for not a single word to explain at this moment
before us had the confidence in central axes of the Special
the premier class in Germany in Aschaffenburg Casino tek parca 36 Leipzig
BINGO
2043-8176-33
Where is Benjamin?
we dont no..
Where were u?
Benjamin!!!
leave me alone now
you're an a********
a nobody?
a nobody!
other has had no idea that i have the encrypted data from the server
First, the printer had manipulated afterwards had a central communication protocol,
the internal firewall to Cracked safety net and from the archive data when the system is considered and backdoor was in two minutes 23s
who ever did is a genius
they have entered the building we have times Delete Video Files
but everything has a consequence
good Morning
What I do not need you might be out.
I I need not point out that it does not help anything. Nothing but you fucking Blender
you can do it people take advantage of Monopolies
quiet for a time
QUIET!!
the body of acting under the pseudonym krypton Neckarsulm was this morning seems to understand his death last night with the removal Hacker attack on the German secret service.
Ideas BND with the cozy biggest scandal in its history
with the corpse was the stolen data material of the BND Hack was found
it is strictly confidential relation care decrypt online undercover agent of the BND card
this is so far vocals. Heath hackers grouping seems to be Fri3nds
BND funded and thus the taxpayers criminal hackers
at this stage can only say that I clear the hacker group clay breaking into the BND system
what was that?
what did you do?
which data did you sent?
they cant prove anything
suddenly all got clear
MRX had to delete the data, once sold them to the russion cyber mafia
MRX is FRI3NDS...
first with the killing, then on for what..
This is your fault
Russian Brand
Embedded map and the courts has been eliminated
Ok
what is the use of this
I do not know
The Rise and Fall of hacker collectives
celebrated as pop stars and Robin Hood of the hacker scene
and now linked to the Russian mafia from the upper hacker
we ask the question... ara we being played
Stefan
..wait!!
this is my duty
this is my fault..
i will fix this
don't you understand?
we I mean you..
oh my god are you alright?
we had MRX
and I was the kitchen
Become so paranoid Ivan the use of other public access points
no!!
we seek everywhere
come..
I am responsible.
they are no different from The rest
i'm sorry.
who is MRX?
What was your plan?
changed its identity for freedom and way. It is doing
do not forget my case it is we shift the invisible
for access to MRX hosts must get to grab the deep bag of tricks
In the other program does Stefan pregnant(trojan) horse
in his Trojans Trojans at the moment and login access to the euro pool server would you access the computer
and MRX mask
i need an hour
i have to apologize for previously..
The known all along that you meant to me it's a shit
I...
shit
sorry..
I'm ass
who were on their way to The Hague to Europol.
Must be in the lion's den III SUVs from ox Darmstadt jealousy of old values phishing methods
and we even tried the drain.
You have to admit that it was impossible to European countries.
I was to blame for everything
I have us out again
it's time to do some social engineering
Power Box I could outsmart the wifi network
with a parallel second network identifier
a so-called Evil Twin
After this when someone else at the office are signin to the network
I would find your last login access
then I Can access the laptop.
Bingo
MEX has an Internet an access code for a tag for the dark net, enter the playback take place
I must now manipulate and pass the Trojans to MRX
as far as he would sign so from the euro pool server would drop his mask
but MRX has our third chance
MRX found the game
and I lost everything
I have to find it again
Martin is Anne call me as soon as you are awake
come here at once
you came
you told me
is out to many possibilities are there but you can be
foundation
I'm blown away
what do you know about me?
you become invisible again
but the Friends know who you are
want a new identity and the  Wilhelm II Protection Program
That's what all the time here.
for that I give in the MRX
and FRI3NDS
Defrance
its is not that simple
the Special Commission successfully Political Media are pleased reality
tell me I get the point
we have him
is a real name
John Lennon.
In a few hours you're a free man.
my name is Neustadt
I would like to ask a few questions
you know this person?
No
Benjamin Engel?
you two went to the same class
Benjamin Engel..
ah yes the Freak
Accompanying grown Knights Templar story your mother is man's life Benjamin is intense and it is the little grown up. your mother is under a dissociative identity disorder
schizophrenia?
Multiple personality.
Personalities all I myself..
Is this hereditary.
something triggered This
Scalpels predispositions are his assets
drugs can strengthen the symptoms
several triggers
but why the questioning?
is Benjamin's ok?
Bullet is from the Second World War?
Yes
where did you get this wound the hand has been injured
It was you..
no
they are dead
there are no bodies no trace N damn bodies in The House
Have you really seen in the hotel room.
i do not know
this means our agreement
is no longer valid
i'm sorry
I have not betrayed
you're child
wait..
one more thing
can you teach me the trick?
Best Social Engineering Trick I'v ever seen
ok I'm Benjamin
I am a hacker.
This is my story
they have all my data
you still one of us
do not let me down
Please enter the information comes in bits and pieces the whole thing really works by itself it
No magic tricks.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
-Pleasse improve this sub-
-Transcribed online using audio-
-Translated using google translator-